CURRICULUM VITAE

PERSONAL DATA

Name : Ahmad Sidik

Home Address: Jl. Sukawarna 1 no.39 rt.02 rw. 01 kel. Pajajaran

Kec.cicendo bandung

Number : 085559001808

Email : ahmadsidik11@gmail.com

Birth Date :12 Agustus 1995



CAREER GOALS

I have worked in the mobile development for 4 years. I think this company is the right place for me to use my technical skills and think financially. I am very interested in upgrading more knowledge and expertise and trying to contribute as much as possible to the progress of this company.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

2015 – 2018 Politeknik Pos Indonesia, Bandung http://:www.poltekpos.ac.id

Informatics Managment, Software Engineering

2011 – 2014 SMK Puragabaya, Bandung, Software Engineering

2008 - 2011 SMP Yaqin, Bandung

2002 - 2008 SDN Lanuma Husein 3, Bandung

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mar 2018 – Aug 2018	PT. Bio Farma (Persero), Bandung http://www.biofarma.co.id Mobile Developer Responsibility and achievement: • Make Android application for employee attendance, • Make Android application for attendance permition, • Make API .NET BASED integrated with firebase • Designing DATABASE SQL.SERVER for application android, • Make Android application for Biofarma Motorcycle Club integrated with FB API, Google API, Google Maps
Aug 2018 - Mar 2019	PT. Pilar Timur Teknologi (Digital Oasis), Bandung http://www.digitaloasis.co.id Senior Mobile Developer Responsibility and achievement: • Android Dev application Project (Japan Paramount), • build ui for android project (Japan Paramount)

Mar 2019 – Mar 2020	PT. Indocyber Global Teknology, Jakarta
	Senior Mobile Developer Responsibility and achievement: • Android Dev in Cash Management BTPN Syariah, • Android Dev in Software BTPN Syariah
Mar 2020 - Now	PT. Deptech, Jakarta Senior Mobile Developer Responsibility and achievement: • Android Dev in Cash Management BTPN Syariah, • Android Dev in Collection Software BTPN Syariah • BackEnd Java And Kotlin Dev in Collection Software BTPN Syariah

SKILLS

Computer Skills:

- Android Studio 9.0 very expert
- SQL SERVER 7.0 expert
- PHPMYADMIN 8.0 very expert
- Visual Studio 7.0 expert
- Firebase 6.5 middle
- Oracle 5.5 middle
- Microsoft Office applications (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- Adobe XD 7.5 expert
- Adobe Photoshop 7.5 expert

Skills And Library:

- Java, Kotlin, PHP, XML, HTML, CSS, Jquery, AJAX, Bootstrap,
- Kotlin, Coroutine, RXJava ,RXKotlin, Navigation Controller, Data Binding, Butterknife, DB Sqlite, Sql Plus, Firebase, Realm, Greendao , Retrofit2, Dagger, Universal Image

- MVP, MVVM
- Indonesia
- English

Certification:

• Internasional Oracle Fundamental 11g - 2018

SELF COMPETENCE

- Able to work in a fast-paced environment
- Good ability to communicate orally and in writing with extraordinary attention to detail
- Very organized and creative
- Very enthusiastic to start work and contribute well to the team

Interst And Hobby

• Coding and Cycling